Sibyl score...
See, what is the problem with a Sibyl score?
You are forcing me to tell the exact score.
Ok.
Means, it should be more approximate?
No. Here, we need a drop down.
750 to 780.
Means...
730 to 750.
You remove the windows.
Ok.
But it should be like that.
Because...
What happens is...
Means...
I feel that...
I need to know the exact score.
Plus, I feel that we need to throw a little.
Yes.
If I have 759...
Means...
I have 780, you can tell me.
No problem.
But it changes in those 10 ranges.
10 ranges?
Then you put it in 10 pieces.
No, no. I don't know.
Let's see the second one.
And I don't want to do average.
No, the ones that are in their mind.
Means...
These are there.
Average, high.
Already, they are there.
So, 700 plus is excellent.
They are already there.
Yes.
Means, they take the windows.
There will not be an accurate rate.
They don't change in 10 points.
Yes. But everyone's windows are regular.
Then break it with 55.
Yes, yes.
Then the list gets bigger.
GCF. Yes, yes, yes.
Then what is it?
With 55...
With 55, you get a lot of smoke.
And if you do 10 with 55...
Then what rate do you want to take out of 10?
Because...
Ok, you suppose...
900 top score.
Do you know what I mean?
It becomes critical.
Then can you give an approximate?
Not approximate, bro.
Because...
I don't have any approximate here.
You want it accurate?
Yes.
Means, you...
Now you will say approximate.
And then you will put a star on the bottom.
That actually you will get the result of your invalid.
Then why are you throwing it to me?
Not approximate.
Ok.
But this...
First of all, everyone knows the exact score.
And...
And then what I feel...
Bro, every point will be consequential.
Yes, then let's see it clearly.
Yes, let's see it clearly or...
I feel that...
I mean...
I have 776 also.
Show me the offer of 780
and I will negotiate with the offeror.
So you tell them that there is not much of a consequence.
Ten windows work here and there.
You have to give me an assurance.
That bro, ten goes ahead.
Same here.
Don't throw so much.
You have to throw 776 or 778.
But the rates change with the banks.
Even if two banks are new, they will have to wait for ten minutes.
Yes.
But which bank...
Where is the breakout?
Suppose one bank says 800 to 810.
Then one bank says 850 to 812.
They say so.
They don't do it in parallel.
Everyone has 810 or 810.
Not everyone.
What does it mean?
Minimum Sibyl Score.
What is the main thing?
You don't want to put the exact.
That is the main concern.
The main thing is that I feel that
I will change a lot in one or two points.
He is changing in real life.
Thinking.
What is the main thing?
What is the problem?
Once I actually have to go.
I feel that I will increase the loan interest.
And hopefully.
How much do you want?
This is what I feel.
If I have 750.
But I feel that
How much do you want?
Tell me.
Then I will take it.
Tell him not to give so much stress.
I don't know so many 5-10 points.
But I fall down a lot.
At least.
What is my score?
You are putting the minimum out.
I know that these offers are relevant.
If I increase the score, it will be better.
No mean.
Civil score.
But no.
Civil score is the same.
Where do I get the minimum?
What is my minimum score?
There is no difference in the approximate.
No.
What is the approximate?
Then the lower results are also approximate.
Suppose I have 766.
Now you have given me 500.
Then I know that
1-2 points are ahead.
I don't remember my score.
But it was average.
1-2 points are ahead.
Then let it go.
But you always say that
one point should not be perfect.
When a person puts 766,
then the drop downs are open.
When he puts 7,
then the next 5-5 drop downs of 7
are open.
And then it keeps decreasing.
There are such searches on Amazon.
If you put a football,
the football is 24 inches.
In the next HS selection,
all such things are selected.
And here we
give a range
but do not give a drop down.
Where?
Like now,
if you put 766,
then the bottom is open.
But the person who has seen it before
will think that you should put it in action.
But you should not put it in action.
How do you tell him?
You have to select it in the drop down.
For that, you have to tell him
that you have to write it.
You have to write the range.
But you should not give him a drop down option.
Either he should select the drop down.
Yes, yes, yes.
Or it should be very big.
Here you should not give him a drop down option.
But you have to tell him that
this is a window.
Yes, it is a window. If you type it,
the window will not open.
Like it is normally done in Amazon.
When you type F, it freezes.